Meeting that special someone can be a real adventure.
Ghosted is a action, comedy, romance film directed by Dexter Fletcher.
Salt-of-the-earth Cole falls head over heels for enigmatic Sadie—but then
makes the shocking discovery that she's a secret agent.
Before they can decide on a second date, Cole and Sadie are swept
away on an international adventure to save the world.
Cole Turner, played by Chris Evans.
Sadie Rhodes, played by Ana de Armas.
Leveque, played by Adrien Brody.
Wagner, played by Mike Moh.
Mom, played by Amy Sedaris.
Dad, played by Tate Donovan.
Ghosted is a 2023 American romantic action comedy film directed by Dexter Fletcher and written by the writing teams of
Rhett Reese and Paul Wernick, and Chris McKenna and Erik Sommers, from a story by Reese and Wernick.
The film stars Chris Evans, Ana de Armas, Adrien Brody, Mike Moh, Amy
Sedaris, Tim Blake Nelson, Marwan Kenzari, and Anna Deavere Smith.
Produced by Skydance, it was released by Apple TV+ on April 21, 2023.
Despite receiving generally negative reviews from critics, it
became Apple TV+'s most watched film debut.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia),
secret mission, secret agent, female spy, enigmatic.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.